<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Caption Irish</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Log in -></string>
    <string name="action_register">Sign up</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Log in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="invalid_email">Invalid E-mail Format</string>
    <string name="invalid_actCode">Invalid Activation Code</string>
    <string name="login_wrong">Wrong username or wrong password</string>
    <string name="no_user">User doesn\'t exist</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Maps</string>
    <string name="title_account">Account</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Disaster</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Report</string>
    <string name="register_nickName">Username</string>
    <string name="register_email">Email</string>
    <string name="register_phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="register_idCode">Identification Code</string>
    <string name="register_password">Password</string>
    <string name="api_key">AIzaSyDrYjvowVSGRHTyi5vO7CZx2Py32G1BoaY</string>
    <string name="register_password_comfirm">Password Confirmation</string>
    <string name="map_id">9c66b1a8c682aabb</string>
    <string name="activation_code">Activation code is used to activate officer account, Users without activation codes are automatically registered as citizen accounts.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_disaster_details">DisasterDetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"


        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>